<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ANF Blogs</title>
    <link>https://anf.myst.rs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ANF Blogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ANF/&#34;&gt;ANF&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 15:45:18 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anf.myst.rs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction into C# and setting everything up</title>
      <link>https://anf.myst.rs/tutorials/csharp/00_introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 15:45:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anf.myst.rs/tutorials/csharp/00_introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Oh, hello there! I think you&amp;rsquo;re interested in learning C# (pronounced as &amp;ldquo;See Sharp&amp;rdquo;). Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck because ANF is planning to make tutorials and write some tips on C#. For those of you who like to interact through video, no this series will most likely never be based on video. There shall be nothing but plain text to read. So I hope you like reading!
Before we get into this, I want to give you a quick disclaimer that I am no C# professional and I am only really just going to teach you everything that I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Null Reference Exception</title>
      <link>https://anf.myst.rs/tutorials/unity/nullref/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 09:32:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anf.myst.rs/tutorials/unity/nullref/</guid>
      <description>As a beginner, at some point or another, you must have encountered null reference exception while developing your application and, for some people it&amp;rsquo;s really hard to understand how to fix it (mainly because, in my opinion, some game devs do not have prior knowledge of C#). So today, you&amp;rsquo;ll be learning how to fix it, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to simplify it as much as possible. So first of all, I want to start off with null reference exceptions because well, it&amp;rsquo;s a really common programming mistake and commonly repeated especially by beginners, so I am going to guide you through about what this &amp;ldquo;Null Reference Exception&amp;rdquo; is and how to fix it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://anf.myst.rs/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 14:20:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anf.myst.rs/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, from the ANF team!
Welcome to the very first blog! This is where we will be writing about updates on new and current projects and tutorials. We are currently working on 4 projects, most open source and free to view and try out.
We are a small team of passionate developers trying to contribute to the open source community. ANF is the organization where @ANF-Studios has his main repositories, so you can check those out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://anf.myst.rs/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 09:55:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anf.myst.rs/projects/</guid>
      <description>Current projects This blog  I really want to write lengthy devlogs and possibly even tutorials, it just really helps people out and.. I love teaching, and I like to see a smile when someone is helped out.  pastemyst-rs  Cover all the required features and finally bump it to version 1. Possibly write a custom implementation of an http request or switch to one that doesn&amp;rsquo;t send a Result&amp;lt;&amp;hellip;&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
