<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ANF Blogs</title>
    <link>https://anf.myst.rs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ANF Blogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ANF/&#34;&gt;ANF&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 09:32:38 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anf.myst.rs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Null Reference Exception</title>
      <link>https://anf.myst.rs/tutorials/unity/nullref/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 09:32:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anf.myst.rs/tutorials/unity/nullref/</guid>
      <description>Okay so first of all, I want to start off with null reference exceptions because well, it&amp;rsquo;s a really common programming mistake and commonly repeated especially by beginners, so I am going to guide you through about what this &amp;ldquo;Null Reference Exception&amp;rdquo; is and how to fix it.
So, why does null ref (short for null reference exception) even happen? Well, the simplest answer for this could be that C# throws this exception when one of your variable is null which basically means</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://anf.myst.rs/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 14:20:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anf.myst.rs/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, from the ANF team!
Welcome to the very first blog! This is where we will be writing about updates on new and current projects and tutorials. We are currently working on 4 projects, most open source and free to view and try out.
We are a small team of passionate developers trying to contribute to the open source community. ANF is the organization where @ANF-Studios has his main repositories, so you can check those out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://anf.myst.rs/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 09:55:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anf.myst.rs/projects/</guid>
      <description>Current projects This blog  I really want to write lengthy devlogs and possibly even tutorials, it just really helps people out and.. I love teaching, and I like to see a smile when someone is helped out.  pastemyst-rs  Cover all the required features and finally bump it to version 1. Possibly write a custom implementation of an http request or switch to one that doesn&amp;rsquo;t send a Result&amp;lt;&amp;hellip;&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
